- webking.skymoon0797 @gmail.com
- Date of birth01/03/1994
- **4** +1 (270) 944-3251

Social networks

in

@jinhai-jiang-09a365267

a

live:.cid.93e43f6e19a494a3

Languages

English

Programming Languages

C/C++, C#, Java, Javascript/Typescript, PHP, Python, Ruby

Frontend

HTML5/CSS3

jQuery/Bootstrap

Sass/Scss

React/Redux(Saga, Thunk)

Vue/Vuex/Vuetify

Angular

TailwindCSS/MUI/ElementUI

Pixel-Perfect UI/UX

JinHai Jiang

Full-Stack Engineer

I am an experienced Fullstack Engineer with over 8 years of experience in software development. I have mastered many programming languages including javascript/typescript, php, python, ruby, C#, Java, and am very familiar with frameworks and tools such as React/Vue/Angular, Node/Express/Nest, Laravel/Symfony, Django/Flask, Spring MVC, ASP.net core/MVC and Ruby on Rails. I can work full-time and deliver satisfactory results in time. Thank you.

Education

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

From April 2011 to March 2015

Jilin University Chaoyang District, Changchun, Jilin, China

Work experience

Full Stack Engineer

From January 2021 to December 2022

CUGATE Ltd Belziger Str. 72, 10823 Berlin, Germany

- Developed a platform to deliver video and geolocation data directly to dispatched police officers to decrease response time and increase office safety.
- Created a real-time communication platform for a finance group to syndicate stock market analysis and trade alerts to hundreds of subscribers daily.
- Built a suite of cross-platform desktop apps designed to easily combine, query, and export data from disparate data sources.
- Worked with marketing teams to establish Facebook ads and Google AdWords strategies. Leveraged pixel-conversions to optimize targeting and increase revenue per click.

Senior Software Engineer

From May 2019 to December 2020

Leads Paid Inc. San Francisco, California, United States

- Prepared architectural outline and led implementation of an OAuth OpenID Connect provider, enabling single-sign-on (SSO) to all Prodigy services.
- Migrated existing services from EC2 to ECS Fargate, enabling autoscaling, blue-green deploys, and improving security.
- Reimplemented existing Excel cash flow models as a Ruby on Rails and React application, lowering turnaround time for new models from days to minutes.

Backend

Laravel/Symfony/CakePHP

NodeJS/ExpressJS/NestJS

GraphQL

ASP.NET(Core.MVC)

Spring Boot/MVC

Django/Flask

Ruby on Rails

Wordpress

Shopify

Database

MySQL/MSSQL/PostgreSQL

MongoDB

Agile Development

Git/Github/Gitlab/Bitbucket

Jira/Trello/Asana

CI/CD Workflow

Assets

Agreeableness

Openness

Interests

Finance

Chemistry

Football Games

Work experience

Back End Developer

From August 2017 to April 2019

Efavormart City of Industry, California, United States

- Built a simple, high-performance React application.
- Created pixel-perfect designs with styled components.
- Integrated a context API to handle application state.
- Developed a small React Native application (using Expo) as a proof of concept.
- Wrote a custom REST API library with Context API.

Senior Frontend Developer

From January 2017 to July 2017

Cicada Technologies Inc Greenwich, Connecticut, United States

- Created a proof-of-concept framework for next-gen TV broadcaster apps (front end).
- Developed the server side to work with broadcaster apps using Node.js. Used both REST API and GraphQL for different projects.
- Developed a content management system for news organizations.
 Included features like geolocation and profile management to deliver content that was most relevant for each user.
- Developed tools to build client websites and webs apps using React and Apollo.
- Built the company's website.